Preliminary Guide to the Vera Dunham papers, 1938-1996 MS2200
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Vera Dunham papers
1938-1996
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
MS2200
18.5 Linear Feet
A paper finding aid is available in the reading room. See staff for assistance. The material dates from 1938-96. The material includes manuscripts, publications, translations, reviews, lectures, and notes. The topics include Russian and Soviet literature and social life.
Restrictions on Access
Some records may be restricted.
Acquisition Information
Vera Dunham donated this collection to Gelman in 1998.
Historical or Biographical Note
Vera Dunham (b. 1913) immigrated to the United States in 1940 and became one of the leading specialists on Russian literature. She has done extensive translations of Russian literature, and is the author of numerous articles in literary criticism. She has taught at Wayne State University, the University of Michigan, and Columbia University.
Collection Scope and Content
Please note: this collection is not processed. A paper finding aid is available in the reading room. See staff for assistance. The material dates from 1938-96. The material includes manuscripts, publications, translations, reviews, lectures, and notes. The topics include Russian and Soviet literature and social life.
Collection Organization
This collection is not processed and series have not yet been determined.
- Papers, ca. 1940-ca. 1996 (bulk 1960-1980) (Box 1)
- Papers, ca. 1940-ca. 1996 (bulk 1960-1980) (Box 2)
- Papers, ca. 1940-ca. 1996 (bulk 1960-1980) (Box 3)
- Papers, ca. 1940-ca. 1996 (bulk 1960-1980) (Box 4)
- Papers, ca. 1940-ca. 1996 (bulk 1960-1980) (Box 5)
- Papers, ca. 1940-ca. 1996 (bulk 1960-1980) (Box 6)
- Papers, ca. 1940-ca. 1996 (bulk 1960-1980) (Box 7)
- Papers, ca. 1940-ca. 1996 (bulk 1960-1980) (Box 8)
- Papers, ca. 1940-ca. 1996 (bulk 1960-1980) (Box 9)
- Papers, ca. 1940-ca. 1996 (bulk 1960-1980) (Box 10)
- Papers, ca. 1940-ca. 1996 (bulk 1960-1980) (Box 11)
- Papers, ca. 1940-ca. 1996 (bulk 1960-1980) (Box 12)
- Papers, ca. 1940-ca. 1996 (bulk 1960-1980) (Box 13)
- Papers, ca. 1940-ca. 1996 (bulk 1960-1980) (Box 14)
- Papers, ca. 1940-ca. 1996 (bulk 1960-1980) (Box 15)
- Papers, ca. 1940-ca. 1996 (bulk 1960-1980) (Box 16)
- Papers, ca. 1940-ca. 1996 (bulk 1960-1980) (Box 17)
- Papers, ca. 1940-ca. 1996 (bulk 1960-1980) (Box 18)
- Papers, ca. 1940-ca. 1996 (bulk 1960-1980) (Box 19)
- Papers, ca. 1940-ca. 1996 (bulk 1960-1980) (Box 20)
- Papers, ca. 1940-ca. 1996 (bulk 1960-1980) (Box 21)
- Papers, ca. 1940-ca. 1996 (bulk 1960-1980) (Box 22)
- Papers, ca. 1940-ca. 1996 (bulk 1960-1980) (Box 23)
- Papers, ca. 1940-ca. 1996 (bulk 1960-1980) (Box 20)
- Papers, ca. 1940-ca. 1996 (bulk 1960-1980) (Box 24)
- Papers, ca. 1940-ca. 1996 (bulk 1960-1980) (Box 25)
- Papers, ca. 1940-ca. 1996 (bulk 1960-1980) (Box 26)
- Papers, ca. 1940-ca. 1996 (bulk 1960-1980) (Box 27)
- Papers, ca. 1940-ca. 1996 (bulk 1960-1980) (Box 28)
- Papers, ca. 1940-ca. 1996 (bulk 1960-1980) (Box 29)
- Papers, ca. 1940-ca. 1996 (bulk 1960-1980) (Box 30)
- Papers, ca. 1940-ca. 1996 (bulk 1960-1980) (Box 31)
- Papers, ca. 1940-ca. 1996 (bulk 1960-1980) (Box 32)
- Papers, ca. 1940-ca. 1996 (bulk 1960-1980) (Box 33)
- Oversize folder (Oversize-folder 1)